http://www.kineticceramics.com/privacy-policy/

Kinetic Ceramics is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Kinetic Ceramics site (www.kineticceramics.com) and governs data collection and usage. By using the Kinetic Ceramics site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationKinetic Ceramics collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Kinetic Ceramics also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Kinetic Ceramics. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Kinetic Ceramics for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Kinetic Ceramics site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Kinetic Ceramics public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Kinetic Ceramics does not read any of your private online communications.Kinetic Ceramics encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Kinetic Ceramics so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Kinetic Ceramics is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Kinetic Ceramics and Kinetic Ceramics family of websites.Use of your Personal InformationKinetic Ceramics collects and uses your personal information to operate the Kinetic Ceramics website and deliver the services you have requested. Kinetic Ceramics also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Kinetic Ceramics and its affiliates. Kinetic Ceramics may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Kinetic Ceramics does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Kinetic Ceramics may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Kinetic Ceramics may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Kinetic Ceramics, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Kinetic Ceramics does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Kinetic Ceramics keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Kinetic Ceramics, in order to determine what Kinetic Ceramics services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Kinetic Ceramics to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Kinetic Ceramics websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Kinetic Ceramics or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Kinetic Ceramics; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Kinetic Ceramics, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Kinetic Ceramics website use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Kinetic Ceramics pages, or register with Kinetic Ceramics site or services, a cookie helps Kinetic Ceramics to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Kinetic Ceramics website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Kinetic Ceramics features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Kinetic Ceramics services or websites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationKinetic Ceramics secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Kinetic Ceramics secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementKinetic Ceramics will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Kinetic Ceramics encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Kinetic Ceramics is protecting your information.Contact InformationKinetic Ceramics welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Kinetic Ceramics has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Kinetic Ceramics at info@kineticceramics.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
